Guide to the Coming Up on the Season exhibition records, 1996-2000.
Coming Up on the Season exhibition records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Coming Up on the Season exhibition records, 1996-2000.
6831
3 cubic feet.
Audio Recordings, Legal Documents, Research Materials, Photographs
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Files relating to Coming Up on the Season: Migrant Farmwork in the Northeast include planning documents, research materials, contracts and agreements, and photographs. Also, cassette tapes of interviews with migrant workers.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Riverhill is a consulting firm that develops historical exhibition, interpretive plans for historic houses, and strategic plans for museums, historical societies, and heritage areas. Coming Up on the Season: Migrant Farmwork in the Northeast, an exhibition developed by Riverhill for the Cornell University Migrant Program explored the historic and contemporary role of farm workers and traveled to numerous venues throughout the Northeast for five years. The exhibition was funded by the National Endowment for the Humanities, the Rockefeller Brothers Fund and the New York State Council on the Arts.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Files relating to Coming Up on the Season: Migrant Farmwork in the Northeast include planning documents, research materials, contracts and agreements, and photographs. Also, cassette tapes of interviews with migrant workers.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Riverhill.
Subjects:
Migrant agricultural laborers--New York (State); Migrant agricultural laborers--New Jersey.; Migrant labor--New York (State); Migrant labor--New Jersey.; Agricultural laborers--New York (State); Agricultural laborers--New Jersey.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- "Coming Up on the Season" object worksheets, 1940-1990 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
- "Coming Up on the Season" object worksheets,copies, photo, cassette tape, 1940-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- "Coming Up on the Season" object worksheets o/s, 1940-1960 (Box 1, Folder 4a)
- Long Island Migrant, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Long Island Migrant documents, 1996-2003 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Documents re exhibit, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Grant awards (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Exhibit concept drawing, 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Migrant Exhibition Manual, crate list (Box 1, Folder 10)
- "Coming Up on the Season"- exhibit walk-through (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Exhibition contracts, plans, details, correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Migrant Talk / MAAM (Box 1, Folder 13)
- New Jersey Migrant, 2002-2003 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Long Island Migrant, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 15-16)
- Objects/Images Migrant farm work, 2000-2003 (Box 1, Folder 17-18)
- Exhibition text (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Object in Exhibition - Migrants, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Migrant workers script, Kathryn Grover original, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Unmatched copies of proofs in exhibition - "Coming Up on the Season", 2001 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Migrant photo proofs (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Script and proofs for "Coming Up on the Season", 2000 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Name draft, Kathryn Grover, 2001 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Archive survey, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Luchando por Nuestro futuro Manual de Los Padres, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Exploring African-American History Long Island and Beyond, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Migrant workers New York State, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Migrant workers New Jersey, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Massachusetts, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Connecticut, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Research - Migrant workers, 1985-2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Registrar/Curator files, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Contacts/Meetings, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Geneseo Migrant Center, 1987-2000 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- RMSC (Rochester Museum and Science Center) Alice Mathis, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Migrant workers interview release forms, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Migrant school programs, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Migrant workers curriculum project, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Educational information, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Other Migrant exhibits, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- NEH - general, 1995-1998 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- NEH project directors (meeting and training), 1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Migrant/NEH proposal, 1995-1999 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Cornell "exhibit objects" photos/comments/etc., 2000-2002 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Hammond, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Possible venue contacts, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Installation photos (Box 2, Folder 17)
- New Jersey Historical Society venue - objects and etc. (Migrant) (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Press re Migrant exhibition, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Migrant worker budgets, 1997-2002 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Migrant installation manual (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Migrant - financial, 2001-2002 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- GANY (Gallery Association of New York) facilities report, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Migrants - Cornell University - general and financial, 1996-1999 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Reproduction permission - Migrant, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Loan agreements - Migrant workers, 2001 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Migrant/NYSCA (New York State Council on the Arts) supplemental, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Migrant - other funders (not NEH), 1996-2000 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Migrant interviews New York State, 1994-1999 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Coins of Change, 2000-2001 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Interviews - migrant workers I, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 31-33)
- Migrant exhibit venues, 1995-2000 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Engman, Herb - correspondence, 1995-2001 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Community field workers: resumes and c. v.'s, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Correspondence/proposals, 1998-2001 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Migrants - advisory, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Community Advisory Committee (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Kathryn Grover, 1995-2001 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Grant applications - Migrant workers, 1997-2000 (Box 2, Folder 41-43)
- Exhibit plan notebook, 2000-2001 (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
- Exhibit text notebook (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Cornell Migrant Program NEH interviews of farm workers, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 5-6)